{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "What is the name for the Jewish New Year?",
      "answers": ["Hanukkah", "Yom Kippur", "Kwanza", "Rosh Hashanah"],
      "correct_answer": "Rosh Hashanah"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?",
      "answers": ["6", "7", "13", "0"],
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": " Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?",
      "answers": [
        "Ron Weasley",
        "Neville Longbottom",
        "Draco Malfoy",
        "Hermione Granger"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Draco Malfoy"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "What is the color of Donald Duck’s bowtie?",
      "answers": ["Red", "Yellow", "Blue", "White"],
      "correct_answer": "Red"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?",
      "answers": [
        "King Harvest",
        "Spectrums",
        "Commodores",
        "The Marshall Tucker Band"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Commodores"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Which animal does not appear in the Chinese zodiac?",
      "answers": ["Dragon", "Rabbit", "Dog", "Hummingbird"],
      "correct_answer": "Hummingbird"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?",
      "answers": ["China", "Ireland", "Brazil", "Italy"],
      "correct_answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Which planet is the hottest?",
      "answers": ["Venus", "Saturn", "Mercury", "Mars"],
      "correct_answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Who was the only U.S. President to resign?",
      "answers": [
        " Herbert Hoover",
        "Richard Nixon",
        "George W. Bush",
        "Barack Obama"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Richard Nixon"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "What does the “D” in “D-Day” stand for?",
      "answers": ["Dooms", "Dark", "Denmark", "Dunkirk"],
      "correct_answer": "Dunkirk"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": " In which city can you find the Liberty Bell?",
      "answers": ["Washington, D.C.", "Boston", "Philadelphia", "Manhattan"],
      "correct_answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was the name of Captain Jack Sparrow’s ship?",
      "answers": [
        "The Marauder",
        "The Black Pearl",
        "The Black Python",
        "The Slytherin"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "The Black Pearl"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": " According to Forrest Gump, “life was like…”",
      "answers": [
        "A bag of lemons",
        "A handful of roses",
        "A lollipop",
        "A box of chocolates"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "A box of chocolates"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "Linda and Bob from Bob’s Burgers have 3 kids. Which one of these characters is not one of them?",
      "answers": ["Louise", "Gene", "Jimmy", "Tina"],
      "correct_answer": "Jimmy"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "The British band One Direction (rip) was made up of Harry, Louis, Niall, Zayn, and…",
      "answers": ["Paul", "Callum", "Kevin", "Liam"],
      "correct_answer": "Liam"
    }
  ]
}
